So this message is for all the women who happen to be white that are following me,
who are like, I'm down. I'm freaking down. I don't want to hear you say it. I want to see
you demonstrated. Specifically when it comes to this whole gun violence situation. I'm tired of
hearing about, oh, it's the second amendment. Cut it out. I'm tired of hearing legislators say,
we can't do anything. We've done everything we can. Cut it out. And I'm tired of children dying
from gun violence every day. Cut it out. So all the Hannah's out there, here's what I need you to do.
I need you to show up in Denver, Colorado on June 5th with Here for the Kids to demand Colorado
Governor Jared Polis to ban all weapons in the state and implement a gun buyback program. Yes,
it's going to take an executive order and it's going to take you white women putting your time,
your money and your bodies on the line. For the black kids, the brown kids, all the kids.
Denver, June 5th, Here for the Kids. You can follow Here for the Kids right here and RSVP on their
website. We ain't got no more time for talking. It's time for walking. So I want to see y'all walk,
run, fly, ski, Pilates your way to Colorado. Denver, Colorado on June 5th to end gun violence
because we're all here for the kids.